<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>SeaJay Environmental</title>
    <link>https://seajayenv.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SeaJay Environmental</description>
    <image>
      <title>SeaJay Environmental</title>
      <url>https://seajayenv.com/images/bg.jpg</url>
      <link>https://seajayenv.com/images/bg.jpg</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.146.4</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="https://seajayenv.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://seajayenv.com/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seajayenv.com/about-us/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SeaJay Environmental LLC&lt;/strong&gt; is a small, woman-owned business based in Oakland, California with more than 30 years of experience in project management and policy support to the offshore energy sector and other blue tech industries. We specialize in managing multi-agency, complex, one-off, and/or controversial projects with hand-picked teams of senior and principal-level consultants. The team is designed specifically for your project, which ensures the highest level of support and expert advice to meet on-time deliverables under a cost competitive business structure.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://seajayenv.com/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seajayenv.com/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SeaJay’s principal environmental consultant is Carliane Johnson who founded the company in 2007. She received her Bachelor of Science degree in Biological Science from Florida State University in Tallahassee. If you hire SeaJay, Carliane is directly involved in every project. She is known for her ability to collaborate and manage across multi-functional teams with efficiency and great attention to detail.&lt;/p&gt;






&lt;img src=&#34;https://seajayenv.com/images/cjohnson.jpg&#34;
     alt=&#34;Carliane Johnson&#34;
      width=&#34;300&#34; 
      height=&#34;260&#34; &gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:carliane@seajayenv.com&#34;&gt;carliane@seajayenv.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;tel:+4154846985&#34;&gt;+1 (415) 484-6985&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reports</title>
      <link>https://seajayenv.com/reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://seajayenv.com/reports/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;reports-resulting-from-seajay-environmental-project-support&#34;&gt;Reports resulting from SeaJay Environmental project support&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.usbr.gov/uc/progact/amp/amwg/2024-08-22-amwg-meeting/20240822-AMWGMeeting-Minutes-508-AMWQD.pdf&#34;&gt;Glen Canyon Dam Adaptive Management Program - Minutes of the Working Group&lt;/a&gt; (2025)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://documents.coastal.ca.gov/reports/2021/12/Th11b/Th11b-12-2021-appendices.pdf&#34;&gt;Glen Canyon Dam Adaptive Management Program - Minutes of the Technical Advisory Group&lt;/a&gt; (2023)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SeaJay Environmental provided note taking and other administrative support services to this Federal Advisory Committee of the U.S. Department of Interior&amp;rsquo;s Bureau of Land Management (BLM). Congress has mandated that BLM operate the Glen Canyon Dam and regulate the Colorado River to meet various statutory goals. The Glen Canyon Dam Adaptive Management Program is the forum to bring the varied interests along the Colorado River to consensus regarding the protection of downstream resources and the balancing of river operations. Members include federal cooperating agencies, Tribes, Colorado River basin states, environmental groups, recreation interests, and contractors for federal power from the Glen Canyon Dam.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
